marketinout.com 2019-02-21

# MarketInOut.com - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy - Last Updated May 24, 2018 

MarketInOut.com values its relationship with its customers and has the utmost respect for the confidentiality of customer's personal information. 

MarketInOut.com does not sell personal information obtained from its customers to other companies. We respect the privacy of every individual who visits www.marketinout.com and/or purchases its Services. This Privacy Policy is our commitment to transparency in communicating how we collect, use, and disclose the information that is collected from you, the visitor of its website and/or customer as well as the choices you have with respect to the information. 

Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Cookies are small pieces of text used to store information on web browsers. Cookies are used to store and receive identifiers and other information on computers, phones, and other devices. Other technologies, including data we store on your web browser or device, identifiers associated with your device, and other software, are used for similar purposes. In this policy, we refer to all of these technologies as "cookies". 

We use cookies to control the access levels for our subscribers to the MarketInOut.com. 

We use cookies to identify your visits to our Website, and other interactions with our Website. We gather information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, browser type, date/time stamp, and store it in log files. To collect this information, a cookie, a standard feature of a website that allows us to store a small amount of data on your computer to allow our web servers to recognize you, may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Website. 

You can control how websites use cookies by changing your cookie settings (www.aboutcookies.org), but your modification may limit your use and functionality of some of the features on our Website. 

Collection of Customer Information

We may collect and process the following data about you: Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of subscribing to our service and any additional posting material. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

Please note that we do not collect credit card data during transactions for security purposes. That information is encrypted and transmitted during the checkout and update process directly to our Merchant Services. 

How We Use Customer Information

MarketInOut.com uses the information it collects about you in the following ways: 

* To respond to any requests from you regarding sales and support. 
* To contact you regarding any agreements or accepted terms that you may have with us. 
* To provide you with marketing emails, special offers, advertising campaigns, or newsletters. 
* To contact you regarding functionality changes to our Services or Website. 
* To develop new features and functionality to our Services and Website. 
* To diagnose problems. 
* To find and prevent fraud. 
* Process for other purposes for which we obtain your consent. Disclosure of Customer Information

MarketInOut.com will not disclose information about customers to third parties. MarketInOut.com will not share personal information about a customer with other customers. 

MarketInOut.com may share customer information, without the customer's consent, with third parties in the following situations: 

  1. Only in a response to a subpoena or court order. 
  2. In connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, or transfer of all or a portion of MarketInOut.com. 
  3. To protect or defend against fraud, unauthorized transactions, law suits, claims or other liabilities. 
  4. To service providers of MarketInOut.com in connection with the administration and operations of MarketInOut.com and its accounts and other products and services. An example of this would be if our email system is not properly functioning for one particular email, we would need have the email software company help us to resolve the issue. 

Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences

In the MarketInOut.com you can access and correct, or delete your personal information at any time. To request your personal information or if you need assistance accessing MarketInOut.com, please contact us at www.marketinout.com/home/contactus.php. 

Protection of Customer Information

MarketInOut.com restricts access to customer information to those employees and third parties who need to know that information to assist in providing services to our customers. MarketInOut.com maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that guard your customer information.
